I did it
What
With the team leader
I did it
I made it clear
what should i do
Hey
Drink it first
and yesterday
It wasn't just the team leader.
Ah
It's really dirty
Then who was there?
Oh, think about it carefully.
that person
It might not be true, so it's just nonsense
don't do it
I'm going to work
My brother went in well.
That that
Team leader
Did I make any mistakes yesterday?
just now
What is it?
did i do something wrong
Is it a storm or something like that?
ha
Ah, it's a song, it's like this
Issi I
Team leader
There was also Haram
Oh no
What are you doing, team leader?
Oh me, me now
I was writing a resume
Yeah, nothing difficult.
yes
But, team leader
Did I make any mistakes yesterday?
mistake
Don't you remember?
I remember
Yudoha has to come up with that.
Ah
I think it would be a good idea to cut down on alcohol.
Mr. Doha
Oh, that
Did I drink a lot?
How much can you not remember?
Ah that
sorry
Ask me what kind of mistake it was
It’s not something that goes away if you ask.
No
Still, I have to apologize
Oh, I'm going crazy
Well, think about it slowly.
Then I'll hang up. It's work.
Oh yes
Please send your resume by tomorrow.
Yes, I will send it to you and contact you.
It's good, but it's on my left wrist.
and here
again
Okay yes more tempo faster hello
uh uh
hello
western
You came
Your responsibility is here
Teacher Lee Ha-neul
I registered after seeing the player.
I was a fan
Please stick with me just once
No way
You won't regret it, right?
You keep running away
I guess I'm not confident
Just shaving cowardly
Let's stop
If you want to give up, you have to deal with it.
I'll never give it to the other side
I don't have any thoughts of my own either.
People
I don't think so
Brother why
It's not coming in right away.
Oh, you look busy
Wow
That day
It went in well.
Ah
There was also Mr. Haram.
What is it, I'm disappointed
That day I met you
I forgot
No that's it
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. That day, bro.
Looks like you're pretty drunk
Well done chairman
Oh yes, iced cafe latte, less ice
yes thank you
I'll buy you coffee
Please grant me one wish
yes
Not Mr. Haram
Haraam
You can't call me like this
And please speak comfortably.
Ah
yes
It's a wish, it's a wish
Okay
Oh no
Haraam
But I still pay for the coffee
You already paid for the coffee.
Ah still
Welcome
uh
Team leader
From early in the morning
What's going on here
first kiss
Mr. Yoo Do-ha
yes
Ah
I can't concentrate because I'm just at home.
This Japanese translation
I have to send it to you by today.
If you hit it with your feet
You can use it even for a day
No
Still, I have to give it to you accordingly.
Can I help you order?
iced americano
I'll take out
Something like that happened
Can a person be born like this?
Wow
Coffee came out
Mr. Yoo Do-ha
yes
Are you really okay?
Ah thank you bro
This
Are you okay?
yes
When your resume is completed, please send it to me by email.
I'll pass it on
get down
What is it
Oh who is it
Oh no no no no
This is not the time
I really wanted to go here
Go play games in the evening
Bring the side dish container too.
Are you not answering?
Hey hey hey hey
Ah
Why are you broken again?
What should I do?
What
Does harmony include interviews?
What are you saying?
Ah
The interview date has been set
You have until eleven o'clock on the 21st.
Isn't it good?
So what should I do?
Whatever I want to do, I have to go.
you want to go there
They said it was a dream
can i go in
The competition will be enormous.
What would be less regrettable?
Then think carefully.
goal
Hahaha hahaha
Gol hehehe
So shamefully
So, you should have focused
Yoo Dong-ah
yes
Did I do well?
Yes, team leader
Oh, is that right?
I'm sorry, team leader.
You took great care to prepare a seat for me.
I can't go
no
I'm sorry if I'm inconvenienced.
no that's not real
I'm sorry
Next time, I will really buy food myself.
Yes, please keep your promise.
yes
Please enter carefully.
You paid a lot of attention to me
Ah
Did you fail the interview?
Oh, I'm next to you without any pretense of popularity
no hey
you home
Doing this in front of me
not anymore
Why are you doing this again?
I didn't do well in the interview
no
A place recommended by the team leader
I'm worried that I didn't go
I regret it
a little
Not much
Oh, I'm hungry
The rice is
No, let's go get something to eat.
You worked hard
Chicken came out
I'll eat well
Why has it been so long since you came?
Because I'm busy
Ah
Oh, why did you eat fried food?
Ah, let’s eat some seasoning.
Oh, I just hate today, so I have to
No, let’s eat half for now.
Half and half, half and half are good
Eat, eat, eat
uh
Team leader
I stopped by a friend's store.
Enjoy your meal
What are you doing, sit down
Team leader
I'm sorry, I was paying attention to you.
I couldn't speak properly at that time
I think I gave it to you
The position recognized by the team leader
The probability of passing will be high
I know but
But
Since I decided that I should advertise
It was the company I wanted to work for the most.
Even if I regret it
once
I thought I should give it a try.
That's amazing
yes
Much more than I thought
He was a mature and strong person.
Mr. Doha
No, I'm not a kid
Well done
I guess I was acting crazy for no reason.
I'm good at it myself
thank you
Ah, maybe
If you're coming to eat, join us.
Would you like to eat it?
I saw earlier that you didn’t eat anything.
That
I don't think my friend would want it.
No
I won't cover myself either, just wait a moment
That's it
If it’s okay with you, team leader.
I guess we are very close.
two people
We've been friends since we were kids.
friend
Come in
Oh, did I just ask you to drink together?
Would you like to eat it?
Lullaby
In chicken
As the beer drains, I lose it.
Beer is a service, so enjoy it comfortably.
Shall we toast? Ta-da
Oh, those girls too
My head has never been lowered.
I only saw your face, right?
So, if you don’t catch this car,
We have to go there. Let's go.
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh hey
I think that will happen
What are you talking about?
It hasn't happened, but it seems like it will happen.
Hey, it looks like it
Ah, something suddenly happened
That happens
Hey go
Ah, but he deserves it
Hey, let's go. Let's go together.
No, no, let's wake up
Brother, what can I do?
uh
My brother is a knight
I will do it
Still, please give it a try.
Infinite hands holding beer glasses
They say it too much
Since when did you sleep like this?